[Music]
Hey everyone let's eat chicken, today the bones are
good, tasty brother, I will go for 750 per kilo
[Music]
Hey who don't mind eating chicken, let's go and
see the bones in the morning
Hey
[Music] [Music]
[Music] [Music] [
Music]
[Music]
Hey,
listen, do your work
brother, give me the puja,
listen
and
push it, if it's
okay then the team is
playing
[Laughter]
[Music]
Ho hey ho hey ho hey ho hey ho hey ho hey ho hey ho hey
[
Music] [Music]
[Music]
Hello Maluk, I have a
lot of work for two
days, let's see everything
[Music] [Music
]
This
[Music] [Music]
[Music]
Hey look,
bull, police, if the day is big then
see
[Laughter]
the game is on
[Shouting sound]
Look, say, say, say, say, hey,
stay put,
complete your efforts
[Music]
Hey, look
brother  Look hey look hey look at the
miracle
you
protein powder putin
powder
hey
hey take this
money
you khinta you you
mundo
munda
[music]
this
oh [music]
[music]
we all protein powder pill khabi dekh ko
see
you meet me then
go
[music]
yes me
[music] hey hey
who is crying.  hey what's up baby
[music]
hey he is crying hey understand hey he is crying hey
understand
[music]
hey who are you
sleeping hey
[music]
[music] take away
this cloth, take off this cloth
[music]
this [music] [music]
hey demon run run [
music]
[music] [music
]
[music]
hey
all those rekul
[laughs]
no uncle the girl does
n't ask for big things
[music]
[laughs]
take the balls take the balls
[music]
this is the big
muscle protein powder khali hey
fool the whole cow will do some work
[music]
[music] do the
work and
complete it
[laughs]
hey brother hey play listen watch the video you are
completely mad hey
normal kadha 300 mil makda me to neelambadi
kokda 5000
come on come on quickly
forget it listen
listen miracle
you shut up
uncle
also
notiya ko bhi bhi no sorry
sorry
ya  [music]
see
[music]
this